Curriculum Vitae

Luca Parolari

It is so easy to overestimate the importance of our own achievements compared with what we owe to the help of others. -DIETRICH BONHOEFFER

last updated: March, 2024

SUMMARY

I am a 26 year old PhD student at the University of Padova. I'm currently working on generative AI for heavily-annotated data and object tracking in medical domain. I have a deep fascination with blockchain technology and astronomy.

PERSONAL DATA

BIRTH: Brescia, Italy, on October 23th 1997. Italian citizen. Male.

CURRENT LOCATION: Padova, Italy

EMAIL: luca.parolari23@gmail.com
LINKEDIN: linkedin.com/in/lparolari
GITHUB: github.com/lparolari

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/2023-current
12/2022-10/2023
O1/2022-11/2022
11/2019-06/2021
Consultant, on-call consultant, on-call 11/2016-09/2019
PhD Student at University of Padova, Italy
Research Fellow at University of Padova, Italy
Al Software Engineer at Orobix, Bergamo, Italy
CS Teacher at "Camillo Golgi" High School, Breno (BS), Italy
Full Stack Developer at Nexio Informatica, Capo di Ponte (BS), Italy
Software Engineer at Esabit, Cedegolo (BS), Italy
Full Stack Developer at Bliss Coffee Vending, Parma, Italy

......

EDUCATION

2019-2021 | MASTER DEGREE, Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence

University of Padova, Italy Grade: 110/110 cum laude

2016–2019 | BACHELOR DEGREE, Computer Science

University of Parma, Italy Grade: 110/110 cum laude

2011-2016 | DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

ITCG "Olivelli-Putelli" Grade: 88/100

PUBLICATIONS

L. Parolari, E. Izzo, L. Ballan. Annotation-driven Generation of Synthetic Data for Referring Expression Comprehension. *Pre-print, under review.* 2024.

D. Rigoni, L. Parolari, L. Serafini, A. Sperduti, L. Ballan. Weakly-Supervised Visual-Textual Grounding with Semantic Prior Refinement. In 34th British Machine Vision Conference 2023. 2023.

L. Parolari. Weakly Supervised Visual-Textual Grounding based on Concept Similarity. *Master Thesis*. 2021

L. Parolari. Design and Implementation in Picat of a Set Constraint Solver. Bachelor Thesis. 2019.